https://slama.dev/comeback/
So, little girl, you'll run to the store.
I already went.
You'll clean up at home.
I always do that.
You'll count the sales.
Did you sell anything?
No.
Well then, the sales won't be a problem.
And you'll help me with Ozzak.
What happened now?
Praise the Lord Jesus, hail.
Forever and ever, Uncle.
Yesterday he was supposed to close up, and instead he fell asleep again.
Good afternoon, bro, how'd you sleep?
Great, I drooled like a rose, like a rose.
And I even guarded the place for you.
See, I even guard the place for you.
Exactly, this is what's killing our sales.
He does it all the time, why does it suddenly bother you so much?
He's getting better at it.
So say something to him.
And who's the boss here?
You are.
Then deal with it.
I'm going to check on the washing machine.
Bye.
For God's sake, what is that?
That's Eddie.
The Iron Maiden mascot.
Have you lost your mind again?
I wanted people to come in and feel like spending, not have a heart attack.
Relax, bro, this is a sure thing.
Quality sells itself.
Tell me, sweetie, what is this?
Easy, grandma, it's just a puppet.
No, no, not that one.
This one.
Well, that's our salesman.
He looks like the devil.
Thanks, grandma.
Well, I'm also a salesman, so what would you like?
Of course, Highway to Hell.
Angus Young's got a killer guitar riff on that, that's the one.
Really?
And does it also sing about a path through a blooming avenue?
No way, don't worry, there's nothing like that on it.
This is honest metal.
What is it then?
Eva and Vasek.
That's probably what you meant, right?
Certainly.
Little Eva and Little Vasek.
Quality sells itself.
Wimp, I almost had her.
Ozzak.
The customer is king, does that mean anything to you?
No, because my only king is Rock'n'Roll.
Good for you, because my king is the installment plan.
Do you know what happens if we can't pay this off?
No.
Me neither.
But unlike you, at least it gives me anxiety.
Listen, bro, your alphabetical system isn't very clear.
What's unclear about it?
Like the fact that it's not in alphabetical order at all.
Hello, Mr. Pacovsky.
Hey, Lexa.
Hi, Mr. Ozzak.
Hey, kid.
Is Iva here?
Dude, check this out.
New Sabbath greatest hits coming out.
Really?
Man, the best-of of all the best-ofs.
That'll be a blast.
I'll go see her upstairs then.
I have to order that right away, it'll sell itself.
Goodbye.
What is it?
Ozzak, can you please tell me how many copies of the old one sold?
I don't remember.
No?
Then let me tell you.
A grand total of two.
One was taken by you, and the other by some little runt who looks a lot like Lexa here.
Goodbye.
See ya.
So, no Sabbath will be ordered. We're buying Gott and Vondráčková, because they'll at least pay the rent.
Why can you sell records by your friends but I can't sell records by mine?
Ozzak, just because you wear Ozzy Osbourne on your t-shirt doesn't mean you're friends.
No.
Good day.
Greetings, told you.
So, sir, do you know why we're here?
I have no idea, are you interested in something special?
I'd say so.
Mr. Pacovsky, you owe Mr. Hajek 100,000 crowns.
And Mr. Hajek doesn't what?
Mr. Hajek doesn't like that.
But I'll obviously pay him back.
Look, you have a really nice shop.
And you surely wouldn't want some bad people coming in and doing something to it.
Woohoo!
It's the new Sabbath greatest hits.
Well, if you'd like it, I can order it for you.
No problem.
Yeah, I'd really love that.
You know, I'll give you my business card, okay?
Don't give out contact info, I told you.
Mr. Pacovsky here will give us his contact info, won't you?
And he'll nicely sign a new payment plan so Mr. Hajek is happy and doesn't have to send the bad guys.
Good day.
No.
Of course, it's you.
Tommy Pacsy.
Tommy Pacsy?
The famous singer, of course.
Don't know him.
You don't remember? "Soak into me like rain, come blow with me like the wind."
In '87.
Third place at Intertalent.
Right, so the man's a singer and he's famous.
And he can't scrape together a lousy hundred grand for poor Mr. Hajek.
Good day.
Mr. Pacovsky, would you please sign for me?
Excuse me, excuse me, I was here first.
What?
I already asked for that autograph 20 years ago at a concert in Slany.
Some crazy woman pushed me aside back then, but today I won't let anyone push me.
This is ridiculous, I'm here on business.
Oh, and I'm here on vacation or what?
Your last song still rings in my ears.
You soak into me.
You soak into me like rain.
What's all this supposed to mean?
Are we at some song recital or what?
Just sign for me, please.
Stop it, I'm allergic to this.
If he's signing for anyone, it's me.
We can leave if you want.
Sure, but tomorrow.
Tomorrow the bad ones come.
No, in a week.
Lubo, let's go.
You said no names, Fanda.
Tomorrow!
Goodbye.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you so much, lady.
Nice guys, you know.
Especially the big one.
I think, bro, I just got us a regular customer.
A customer?
Yeah.
Those were debt collectors.
They're not going to spend anything here.
They'll come, take what they want, and smash whatever they don't take.
And your CDs will be smashed to bits.
Hi.
Come on, Iva.
I'll leave it open, bro's coming right back.
You two are always together.
Aren't you actually Siamese twins?
Unfortunately not, someone would have to notice that.
Iva, can you see me?
What?
I mean, can you see me?
Did you hit your head?
I feel like I'm invisible.
When I walk down the street, people look right through me.
When I say hello to someone, they don't answer.
My classmates ignore me.
Only ticket inspectors notice me.
But you're just imagining it.
You're just the quiet type, but otherwise you're a perfectly visible girl.
Hi, Iva.
Have you seen Sasha?
My problem is you have a nutcase for a brother.
What is it?
It was a joke, right?
But it wasn't a joke.
Can't you see your sister's depressed?
I can't.
Iva, have you seen Sasha with depression?
Or maybe it's an underdeveloped personality.
Everyone notices Lexa right away.
Yeah, because he's abnormal.
But you're normal.
Normal, but invisible.
What is it?
Nothing.
Can you give me a moment? These are sensitive matters.
Or, and this is the worst part, I start telling someone something and they start dealing with something completely different.
Like the other day I woke up Mom and I told her what should I do, that I feel lonely, that all the girls my age already have boyfriends, that they shave their legs, that they go to discos and at those discos they meet those boys, and nobody notices me even though I shave too.
And I asked what I should do.
And she took a deep breath and said...
Lexa, what are you doing there?
That's exactly what she said.
Nothing?
Don't say nothing.
Look, I know you're attracted to me, that you're obsessed with me, but what you're doing borders on a psychological disorder.
What kind of disorder?
Lexa, show me your hand.
Which one?
Lexa, why do you have Ozzak's underwear?
I wanted to help you.
Hang up laundry.
Oh fine, then please, help.
Sorry, what were you saying?
Simona, one more time.
Tommy, if you would one more time, I mean on stage, soak into me like rain.
Madam, I'm not soaking today.
And I'll soak into you.
I see you keep lowering your standards.
What do you need?
A hundred grand or vodka.
Tom, are you still mad at me?
I did everything right this time.
I quit show business, put my money into a shop, raised a girl, hired my brother.
He did everything right and hired Ozzak.
I'm cutting you off.
Then tell me what to do.
First of all, smile.
Everything goes better with a smile.
Well?
Lexa?
He's completely lost it.
Can you hang white laundry with colored?
Lexa, is that some former pop star too?
No, that's my crazy son.
Takes after his father.
See, your ex is doing well for himself.
He's doing well alright, but with someone else.
He's living it up overseas.
Go to Gott and let him help you.
Beg from Karel Gott?
Never!
Hard to resist, huh?
Well, let's keep her here as a jukebox.
Don't worry, my darlings, I'll hide you and they won't find you.
Hey Uncle, what's going on down there?
Don't even ask.
Some debt collectors want to wreck the place?
How?
I don't know.
They came in and at first they didn't seem bad.
The big one was even interested in Sabbath.
Yeah, if we don't get 100 grand soon, they'll smash my CDs.
That's seriously messed up.
Yeah.
What is that, Mr. Ozzak?
Nothing children's eyes should see.
Porn.
Cool.
Yeah.
Was your dad gay?
Keep your mouth shut.
I knew Dad used to make a living in a weird way, but this weird?
What is he wearing?
Gay clothes.
What else is there, Mr. Ozzak?
Nothing interesting.
The only decent thing in there is that dartboard.
So what else have you got?
I don't think you're ready for this yet.
Uncle, unpack it or I'll tell Dad where you hide Gott.
Some kind of chain.
CDs.
Vitamins?
Vitamins.
Kids' piggy banks were drained by those.
An original Michal David, hide it.
Never speak that name again.
And what's this?
Betamax.
It says "Two Little Wings" on it.
Are they there?
They're not.
See.
You were never supposed to find this.
I know what that is.
You used to burn CDs on it.
The porn is on that.
Welcome to my place.
For the inner circle, press one.
For the outer circle, press two.
Karel?
If you'd like to hear my interpretation of world history, press three.
If you'd like to leave a message, wait for my high C. Hi Karel, this is Tomy Pacsy.
Remember...
How we used to party in Sopot.
Please, I've got a problem.
I need to borrow some money.
I will listen to your message on Sunday, when I rest.
If you'd like advice for today, press the star key.
Never borrow from friends.
The eighties, those were terrible times.
Yeah, Depeche Mode fans.
Vitezslav Vavra.
Marketa Muchova.
Pavel Hornak.
Spartakiad.
Yeah, we know him.
We learned all this in school, right?
No freedom, oppression, Gorbachev, then they locked up Havel.
Then they burned Palach.
There was a revolution.
Velvet.
I can see you've got that down, but what's in the textbooks isn't what matters.
Just one document like this is enough to understand what brainwashing was.
You soak into me like rain and I'll soak into you.
Such happiness you won't find, you'd go all the way to heaven.
You'd carry me away like a hurricane, I wouldn't care that I don't know where.
You soak into me like rain.
You saw nothing and you remember nothing.
I actually kind of liked it.
He needed money.
Yeah, but what a disgrace.
A disgrace.
Lexa, what did you say people spend the most on online?
I don't know, but I spend on dirty stuff.
Dirty stuff?
Nothing gets burned.
People are perverts and all this stuff can definitely sell well.
Sure, people buy all kinds of crazy stuff these days, you'd be surprised.
Like photos of my sister in the shower.
What?
That can't be, you little brat.
Jesus, buddy, what are you doing here?
Hey Standa, look, this is really embarrassing, but I need to borrow some money.
Sure, how much do you need?
Well, exactly, 100 thousand.
I really would, I really would, in '88 you pulled me off the shovel.
But I don't have it.
I'm expecting expenses.
Yeah, meet them.
Majda, Lenka, and Bolenka with Veronika.
This camera.
How do you get it online?
Easy.
We take photos, connect to the computer, upload to the server, add a comment and wait for the first post.
Got it?
Hey, what's this here?
What?
This label that says "Sexy Lexa."
Nothing.
Just some link.
And why is my photo on it?
It was already there.
That's our shower.
Lexa, how could you put naked photos of your sister online?
It was easy, I just connected to the computer and uploaded to the server.
And why is there so much writing in that weird script under my picture?
Classic, Vietnamese discussion forum.
If you can get rich on photos anywhere.
I mean, on these record collector sites, that's the place.
Someone is discussing me there?
What are they saying?
They're pretty complimentary.
What are you talking about, since when do you speak Vietnamese?
What are automatic translators for?
Sasha, click the green circle.
I would like not just look but also touch.
What do you mean?
Don't worry, Sasha.
There's probably something better too.
Well, like that one there.
She so pretty, I cry right away.
See?
Well, "cry" has multiple meanings in Vietnamese.
I cry for you four times in a row.
Let me explain that to you right away, Sasha.
I very much like your water rodent.
I guess they really do like me.
Well, it's true that the Vietnamese might buy it.
Not just the Vietnamese, the whole world shops there.
Sasha is upstairs chatting with them right now.
Which Sasha?
She's my sister.
You have a sister?
Sure, my twin.
Bring her by sometime.
Bro, so what?
Got the cash?
Don't worry, Dad.
We're trying something and if it works out, you'll have enough to pay.
Enough to pay?
How?
Legally.
Let the girl know how cruel the world is.
Can someone explain what's going on here?
Now we can, we managed to sell your old junk over the internet.
What junk?
You know, that suitcase full of stuff in the hole in the wall.
What?
You sold my personal belongings.
Do you have any idea what those things are worth?
More than a hundred thousand.
A hundred thousand for that?
A hundred thousand for a whole human life, for my dreams, for my memories?
A hundred thousand?
Did you say a hundred thousand?
Yeah.
In that case, we're saved!
That's incredible!
Where are you?
One of my fans.
I just made the best purchase of my life.
What purchases?
I bought relics from your artistic career.
Everything's there.
Posters, genuine Michal David CDs.
I'd like to donate it all to you.
Throw out this junk and make your own museum here.
People will come here like to Graceland.
Wait, you're the one who bought it?
Yes, it was almost free.
A hundred thousand Vietnamese dong.
How much is that in crowns?
About a hundred.
You idiot.
A hundred crowns for my entire past?
Doesn't my life have more value?
What should I say, Mr. Pacovsky?
Such fantastic shower photos.
For a lousy two crowns.
Aren't you happy?
Miserable woman.
In a few hours the debt collectors will be here and I might lose my life.
At least she knows it's not worth much.
I'm still here.
Here we are, and now it's getting serious.
Who doesn't belong here?
Out!
Out, scram!
So what are we playing today, Lubo?
You said no names, Fanda.
Shut up and show me the bag.
Golf?
I prefer baseball.
I got you those Sabbath CDs.
I told you what?
What did I tell you?
What did I tell them, Lubo, what?
You told them, Fanda.
Exactly, I told you the bad guys would come.
And here they are, see?
All done here, let's go to the store.
I know you from somewhere.
Apparently this isn't your first experience with seizure.
Colleague, let's continue the asset inventory.
Excuse me, but what's this supposed to mean?
Mr. Pacovsky owes an enormous amount of money.
Yes, he does.
But to the state. If you represent a private creditor, contact the bankruptcy trustee.
But Mr. Hajek...
Will have to wait.
First in line is the Ministry of Finance, the bank, the Ministry of Interior, the Ministry of... Debts.
Are those baseball bats yours?
Those are ours.
And this junk?
Is there any business connection between you and Mr. Pacovsky here?
No, no, no, we have absolutely nothing to do with this.
We're just, you know, here by chance, just, just passing through, and now we're leaving, right, goodbye.
Gentlemen, gentlemen, and that car outside, is it yours?
That's Lubomir's here, goodbye.
That's that.
Marcelka, you're a genius.
And not just in this.
No way.
Not a scratch.
I always said Sabbath is the toughest band in the world.
We handled that beautifully.
That's great, friends, but I still need a hundred thousand.
This will be tougher.
So this is what it looks like.
You know, sometimes I have these unlikely nightmares about poverty.
So I came to see what it looks like in real life.
Look, Karel, if you came to make fun of me, then...
I came to give you advice.
If it's free.
Every thing has two sides.
Look, I once painted my first painting on a dartboard just like this.
I was alone in a late-night arcade.
And I happened to have a beautiful, inspiring blonde within reach.
Don't be servile, Marianne.
You calm down too, Rene.
Pity I don't remember what happened to that dartboard.
I may have given it to someone.
It would be worth millions now.
Well, I have to fly.
Bye.
Oh, and one more thing, don't forget.
Every thing has two sides.
How about I thank you, Karel?
Will you come by again sometime?
My ways are mysterious.
He exists.
Ozzak, where did you get that dartboard?
It was with your suitcase of stuff from the eighties.
And for a moment I thought miracles were real.
That woman kept making me nervous.
But I want a new dartboard.