https://slama.dev/comeback/
Sure, I liked it yesterday.
Like, I was all worked up.
What kind of word is that?
Sure, we could continue tonight.
Alright then.
Great.
Bye then.
Who was that?
So, who was that?
What do you want to hear?
Come on, I'm your dad, you can tell me absolutely everything.
Including who that was?
Who was that?
Iva, I mean well.
Trust me.
Well, you trust me.
I do trust you.
Well then everything's fine.
Well then you can just tell me who it was.
Sasha.
And what did you two like so much yesterday?
We liked the movie.
With Sasha.
At the cinema.
And what got you so worked up?
It was about firefighters.
And what do you want to continue tonight?
The movie.
They didn't put out the whole fire.
Mr. Pacovsky, Iva here.
I haven't been able to reach her for half an hour.
Iva, the bell rings in ten minutes.
Iva, how is it that you just talked to Sasha for half an hour, and Sasha can't reach you?
That was a different Sasha.
Different from this one?
You think there's only one Sasha in the world.
Iva, you have another friend named Sasha?
Come on, come on, please, come on.
Hi.
Ivushka, let's go.
What's up?
Ozzak, do you have a minute?
Hold on, I'm operating.
Tomas, did something happen?
Not yet.
Marcelka, please, leave us alone for a moment, okay?
Thanks.
Bro, it's really important.
What could be more important than this?
Take a look.
A phone?
No, read it.
Your battery is almost dead.
What are we going to do?
I have a charger with me.
Marcelka, please, go mind the register, thank you.
I won't forget last night.
I hope we get to know each other more deeply soon.
Bro, I hope you remember something.
I've got a total blackout.
I was wasted.
But some guy is writing this to Iva.
You think he'd send it for approval?
That's not my phone.
Whose is it?
Iva's.
Look, he writes here that he wants to get to know her more deeply.
What do you think he means?
What do you think?
He wants to...
Well, it's about time for our little girl, too.
What?
For God's sake, bro, you wouldn't want her to have to sleep with some fifty-year-old teacher in a closet just so she's not the last one in class.
I'll have that mangy beaver in front of my eyes till I die.
It happened in the biology closet.
Christ, lady, don't do this to me.
Really, Marcelka, go mind the register now.
Thanks.
Iva is not going to do anything.
She's sixteen, she has plenty of time for sex.
Besides, it could leave her with psychological scars.
Please, I lost mine at twelve and I'm totally fine psychologically.
Yeah, but everyone around you is a nervous wreck.
Bro, you're freaking out.
What's the worst that could happen? She gets pregnant and drops out?
I didn't finish school either.
Yeah, but you're not my daughter, you know?
Come on, what's wrong with being a mother at sixteen?
Your mom had you when you were five.
When you were five?
So, here I'm bringing it back.
It's really intense.
You know, good old Urias.
I have to get to school.
Come here then.
Do you know anything about the guy Iva's dating?
Iva isn't dating anyone.
No?
Then read this.
Your battery is almost dead.
Do you need a charger?
I have one.
But nobody wants it.
The teacher in the closet told me the same thing.
Some guy is writing to Iva that he wants to get to know her more deeply.
What do you think he means?
More deeply?
Could it be her gynecologist?
Iva forgot something upstairs, I'll wait for her here.
Sasha, what do you know about the guy Iva's dating?
The truth!
You know about it?
Iva said nobody knows.
That he's a gynecologist.
I don't know, they only had one date.
For God's sake, that's one more than with me.
Iva wanted me to go with them, but I'm too shy for the sauna.
She went to a sauna with him?
Don't worry, nobody saw them, it was just the two of them.
Jesus Christ!
But they weren't there long, then the police showed up and he had to run.
He had to run?
That's insane!
And you know what's even crazier?
That Iva has another friend named Sasha.
Do you know her?
Dad, have you seen my phone?
Isn't it upstairs?
Only yours was upstairs.
Yeah, I hope that when I'm dating someone, you won't tell him you have me saved in your phone as "my little butt."
Yeah, it's not little anymore.
Yeah, yeah.
Dad, you've been going through my phone?
This is how you trust me?
But you've been meeting behind my back with some...
Oh God, I won't tolerate that.
Guy in a sauna.
In that case, exceptions apply.
Sasha, they already knew, I didn't tell them a word.
Just about the sauna and the police, but otherwise not a word.
Yeah, I really confided in the right person.
Whatever.
I can go out with whoever I want and wherever I want.
And it's none of your business, because it doesn't concern you.
But I'm your dad.
A dad doesn't snoop through his daughter's phone.
Only a... ...cop does that.
Let's go.
A cop.
That checks out.
I'm going to smack her.
What does she think she is, the little brat?
That she's a victim and her father is an imbecile.
And you think I should just wait till she gets over it?
She'll get over it at 27, then she'll talk to you normally.
When you babysit her kids.
See, all the more reason to stop it now.
I'll just forbid her from seeing him and that's that.
There's no greater motivation for hooking up than a ban from an imbecile father.
So is there any way at all to prevent this?
Tomas, there are only three things that can come between a sixteen-year-old girl and her first sex.
And a father isn't one of them.
Then what?
A stuck zipper, premature ejaculation, and death.
Hi, Simona.
Hi.
How come it's so empty in here?
People don't come in.
I come all the time.
You do.
But you don't pay.
How much?
15 hundred.
And that's not counting the destroyed paneling in the bathroom.
They had a poster of Heidi Janku there.
Couldn't tear it off.
Now I put up Rolling Stones.
You're a fan too?
No.
They had the biggest poster.
Covered the whole hole.
You're a bro.
You're not getting paid.
You're a cheapskate.
So are you.
The girl's acting out and you're not helping me at all.
Me, not helping?
Today I arranged all the CDs in the display by size.
That's so you.
I'm here looking for a solution to prevent the worst, and you're just doing stupid stuff.
I have a solution.
Oh yeah? What?
Let's smoke up.
And what will that solve?
Nothing, but we'll feel good.
See that?
That's your irresponsible attitude.
Let me tell you, you don't even care about the girl.
Me, not care about her?
I love her like, like Metallica.
Like her own father.
If you loved her like her own father, you'd talk to her.
Then I'll talk to her.
Really?
A serious conversation?
Everything!
Father to daughter.
Fine, but I'll start.
I have a certain responsibility for you.
Look, at 16, a person isn't mature enough to understand all the consequences of their actions.
They can last a lifetime.
Or just two doses of penicillin.
Look at Aunt Simona.
What does she have to show for her life?
You want to end up like her?
Well, since she stopped working the night shift alone, she can at least sleep during the day.
Well, it's not about Aunt Simona, it's about you, of course.
About your future.
What's the guy's name?
I'd say he has a male name.
I was asking Iva.
Iva didn't say anything.
Because you were the one talking.
The worst thing is silence.
What does that have to do with anything?
Iva, always talk things out, so you don't end up like us.
Don't listen to this.
Then make up.
What?
Well, he should use a condom and she should wash up first.
Are you crazy, do you know what you just said?
Alright, he should use a condom and you both wash up.
Great, that's really great.
Ozzak, please, leave us alone now.
No, no, no, you'd yell at her.
I wouldn't!
You're yelling!
I'm not yelling!
You're raising your voice.
Fine then, Ozzak, this is between a father and daughter, you don't need to be involved.
I'm the dad, that's what we agreed.
No, I'm the dad, I'm canceling the deal.
Iva, pick your dad.
What do you mean?
What kind of nonsense is this, for God's sake?
Which of us two will explain it better, huh?
Want the version with the bees?
Or a proper Ozzak-style drinking session with video examples, huh?
Well, listening to you two, I can promise you only one thing.
Well?
That we'll wash up.
At least that's something.
Sex everywhere.
Well, you can't really blame people.
It's really disgusting what's being thrown at us.
Nice one.
My little hottie.
What if somebody licks it?
That's crazy, huh?
What can I get you?
Do you have Sex Pistols?
Nice shop!
That's just crazy, huh?
They opened a new stand across the street.
Watch out for me.
Look at this.
Somebody slowly threw some trash here.
Well, if you'd come on time, you could have been inside long ago.
If I'd been inside, Mr. Pacovsky, I couldn't have seen what I just saw.
Is nobody going to ask me what I saw?
I saw Iva with some guy.
What?
That he's a gynecologist.
I've seen him somewhere before.
Try to quickly remember where you saw him.
In a store?
On a tram?
At the gynecologist's.
Lexa.
In prison?
Ozzak.
Birthday party.
My birthday party.
A relative of yours?
Oh my God!
Oh my God, speak, you unfortunate woman!
He was the stripper who jumped out of the cake at me.
Like, completely naked?
No, at first he had this police cap and a really big baton.
Tomas, wake up.
What is it, what is it?
Was I sleeping?
Well, something like that.
What a relief.
I dreamed that some boy invited Ivushka on a date to a sauna and then Marcelka came saying he's a stripper.
That wasn't a dream.
That's practically a porn actor.
And why couldn't Ivushka bring home a stripper?
They don't spend money on clothes.
He's out every night, so he doesn't need a bed, and we could use him to attract girls.
And hasn't it occurred to you that it could be the other way around?
That he'd take her away?
Mr. Pacovsky, am I understanding correctly that Iva has a boyfriend?
Wait, as in he'd take Ivushka away from us?
Lex, what are you doing here?
I borrowed keys from a buddy.
Ozzak shouldn't have his own keys.
Sis, don't you want to leave?
She doesn't.
Sis, at least turn around.
Have you ever seen anything like that?
I have.
You were trying it all last night.
Dad's going crazy.
He just took my phone and read your text message.
Man, if someone touched something of mine, they wouldn't survive it.
I'd have a blackout.
And when I have a blackout, I lose control.
But he didn't mean it badly.
He's just worried about me.
No comment.
That's the big downside of still living with your dad.
I was on my own feet right at eighteen.
But you're only twenty?
Well, almost.
Then it's high time, want to move in with me? I've got a place.
Not really, not yet.
But I'll think about it.
Well, you know, who would take care of Dad and Uncle.
So Robert, what do you like to do?
I really love going to the gym.
Comes in handy at work all the time.
So what do you do?
I'd rather tell you once we get to know each other a bit better.
You know how it is.
Why all this secrecy about your work?
Some people react to the job.
I feel so much calmer when you put it like that.
But it's nothing scary.
It's just that people have a lot of prejudice about us.
Look, it's a job for real men.
I need a fit body, strong nerves, endurance.
Tonight I still have to go to work.
I've got my uniform with me.
I see.
Yesterday around this time I had a call at an apartment.
Some old woman was lying there.
Not a pretty sight.
Tomas?
Mr. Pacovsky!
Ozzak!
Ozzak, for God's sake, what's going on here?
Ivushka is leaving us.
What, already today?
Today or tomorrow, a stripper or a teacher.
Our little girl is gone and there's a grown woman in her place.
And she'll leave us too, like all women.
Don't worry, I won't leave you.
Never mind then.
Mr. Pacovsky, I have bad news and good news, which do you want to hear first?
The bad news?
Is Iva dead?
She's not dead.
She went to the Jezevec for a date with the stripper.
Now the bad news.
And the bad news is.
Wait, Mr. Ozzak, now you've confused me.
That was the bad news.
What's the good news, Lexa?
Iva isn't into strippers at all.
Really, I tested it on my own skin.
A hundred percent.
The guy is definitely hiding it from her.
When we expose him in front of her, she'll dump him.
Like she dumped me.
I'm not entirely sure it's the stripper, though.
But...
But you said it was him when you saw him.
I saw him, but with clothes on.
And besides, at the birthday party I wasn't exactly looking at his face.
Then where were you looking?
That doesn't matter at all.
Three things can come between Iva and sex, and I'm not one of them.
Don't worry, I'll stand between Iva and sex.
Right, let's go to Iva and tell her everything.
We'll open her eyes.
We'll expose the parasite that's latched onto her.
Of course, Lexa, let's go.
Us too.
For God's sake, why me?
For identification purposes.
Bro, you coming too?
So who's the better dad now, huh?
Let's go.
That's weak.
Hi, this is Tomas Pacovsky.
Remember me?
Yeah, would you have a minute?
I don't know.
For God's sake, why did we bring you along?
He did have a distinguishing mark, but we can't see it from here.
Let's sit at a closer table then.
That won't help.
He had a tattoo on his butt.
So, a manly guy?
On the contrary, he was very manly.
Too bad.
You're a real friend.
I don't even know why I'm supporting you in this.
You're just sitting here feeling sorry for yourself.
Tomas, pull yourself together.
Every trouble has its limit.
But she's the only thing in my life I truly care about.
Then do something about it.
If you really care about her, you have to get moving.
You're a dad, so fight.
You mean it?
Why give up the match at halftime?
That was beautifully said.
Yes, why indeed.
And it even rhymes.
See?
I like you better like this.
Yes, we need to go right away.
Yeah, please.
Aren't you hungry?
We've got sausage goulash in the oven.
In what situations does an adult man take off his pants?
They're about to pay, so probably soon behind the corner in the park.
Mom, you have to think of something.
I've got it.
Mr. Ozzak will dress up as a doctor and go give him an injection.
Do you see what I see?
Good evening.
I'm Tomas Pacovsky, father of Iva here.
What are you doing here?
Being a dad.
Nice to meet you.
I came to tell you that I don't approve of what you do for a living, and that you should have more decency and not get involved with decent and inexperienced girls.
I don't do anything I should be ashamed of, Mr. Pacovsky.
And at home?
What do they say about your profession?
Mom's proud.
Well, you're quite a strange family.
Excuse me?
Dad, please, stop.
Easy, Ivushka, this is between me and this gentleman.
And me too.
No stripper is going to take Ivushka away from us.
You're a stripper?
I'm not.
What kind of nonsense is that?
But he is.
He jumped out of a cake for this lady.
I...
I'm not a stripper.
Prove it.
I'm supposed to prove I'm not a stripper?
Take off your pants.
That would prove I am a stripper, wouldn't it?
That's true, Ozzak.
Why should he take off his pants?
Because...
Where does he have it?
Right here.
Ew.
What's going on?
I'm asking you as the father of my daughter.
Take off your pants so we know where we stand.
Are you all crazy?
Fine, differently then.
Ozzak, hold him.
That's me.
You'll see.
It's him!
Robert, please, don't be mad at them.
You've got a pretty crazy family.
You should decide whether you'll come with me, or keep rotting here with these nutjobs.
That last punch too.
Just don't have a blackout, okay?
To serve and protect.
Do they bring oranges to prison?
Lexa has an allergy, I think.
He can peel them then.
And what do I have to bring him?
When I go visit him.
And what if you run into Robert there?
Robert is an idiot.
I'm glad you're saying that, Ivushka.
You know, I'd have killed you if you kept dating him.
I know, I didn't behave well either, but you were worried about me.
But now I know I'll never tell you who you should or shouldn't date.
That's your life.
How could you let him call us a family of nutjobs?
Come on, in protest let's chain ourselves to the railing outside the precinct.
Count me out, last time we did that, it poured for two months.
Yeah, but we have to do something.
Imagine Lexa being afraid to bend over in the shower for the soap.
Well I'll be, you got busted too.
We're going to chain ourselves to the railing.
Haven't had pneumonia in a while, have you?
In protest against the unjust imprisonment of your son Lexa.
Lexa assaulted a police officer.
In self-defense.
Doesn't matter, when you kick a cop, they always haul you in.
I think what pissed Robert off the most was that he couldn't catch Lexa afterward.
Yeah.
And that he threw his gun into the juice.
He really shouldn't have spit in his face.
A chip off the old block.
I protest.
Something has to be done about this.
My thoughts exactly.
Good evening.
Hey, Mom.
Hey.
Lexa, they let you out already?
Yeah.
I fixed their network and cleaned viruses off their computers.
And I installed a card game for the chief, so he wanted us to be on first-name terms.
He even gave me an application to join the force.
Don't you dare.
What would people say?
Robert would be especially thrilled.
Robert's in trouble.
Apparently it wasn't the first time.
Uncle chief said they're going to fire him.
Dude.
Stop it, or I'm going to cry.
Alright, take care, jailbird.
We need to find Sasha.
You think she can just disappear whenever she feels like it?
Shall we go?
Can I come over to your place for a bit?
You'll tell me all about it.
That kid's going to be somebody someday.
Bro, why won't you take that off?
I already chained myself to it.