https://slama.dev/comeback/
There was no escape from them, today they won't escape from us. God's Mills.
Today we peek into the private life of Risa Velen, performer of hits like Dream Brigade, Puppy, and He Called Himself Genghis Khan.
Why has bankruptcy been filed against him?
Who is the mysterious man in the photographs?
Why is he kissing his wife?
Find the answers to all of this in today's episode of God's Mills.
Poor Risa.
Such filth, I won't watch this for even a second.
What, what is it?
I don't know, I'm not watching it.
Is that Uncle Risa?
Why is he crying?
You keep denying your stay at the treatment facility.
I was never in a treatment facility.
So you're denying the stay.
Poor uncle.
Risa Velen.
Madman, violent offender, and even though our team failed to find any bones in his sprawling garden, a practically convicted dog killer.
We've ripped the mask off another pop criminal of the past.
Which star will we extinguish next?
God, please don't let it be me.
Relax.
Pavel Hornak.
At first glance a polished lawyer, and for the second glance watch God's Mills.
Exactly one week from now.
See, there you go.
What is it?
It's over.
Thank God.
Now it'll be him, then me.
I always came right after Hornak.
At the Bratislava Lyre, at Lucerna, except at Rockfest where I was first.
Right.
Who got booed.
Dad, chill, you're not interesting enough for this show.
You don't kill dogs and you haven't been in a facility either.
Iva, wait!
What?
What if they're here?
Who?
Them, God's Mills.
You'll just tell them off, right?
And I'll say no and they'll shoot it without me.
They'll destroy me like they destroyed Risa, and I'll have to live underground.
But if we don't pick up, maybe they'll think we went somewhere.
Hello?
No.
No, he's not mentally incompetent.
Yes, his name really is Ozzak.
Well, it's written in his ID card.
In marker.
So what?
Goodbye.
That was the driving school.
Ozzak actually showed up.
Jesus Christ.
And has anyone told him you can't drink behind the wheel?
Apparently he has a shot beforehand.
If God's Mills finds out, they'll make a two-parter about us.
Iva, what did we agree on?
What's going on?
He confiscated my phone and forbade me from answering the phone.
But not without reason.
They'd destroy us all.
Dad thinks they're after us.
Just like at our house, Lexa also says they're after us.
God's Mills?
No, aliens.
See?
And you say I'm the paranoid one.
Hello, this is Tomas Pacovsky, we've left for Tibet and will never return.
Goodbye.
Damn, what am I supposed to do now?
For God's sake, Mr. Pacovsky, call me, the phone doesn't work.
Marcelka, it's me, calm down.
So...
No, I'm not calling from a monastery, no, no.
I'll explain, wait downstairs.
I have to go to the shop.
Don't answer.
Iva, are you going to Tibet?
There won't be a family vacation, at most a family embarrassment.
And another one at our house.
Did you know that in driving school you have to drive with an instructor?
I didn't.
Just so you know why the police are looking for me.
Wonderful.
Father a paranoid, uncle a car thief.
Who are we still missing?
It's open, Lexa.
Hi, Iva.
I bought this for you.
Now you can carry a banana in your bag and it won't get squished.
You can sit on it and nothing happens.
The Pacovsky residence.
Hello, Mr. Pacovsky.
Yes, is this your apartment?
And your phone?
Well, it was ringing, so I...
But you wouldn't have gotten through.
Then why are you calling if you don't want to get through?
I'll pass it on.
Goodbye.
Iva, Dad says you should bury the phone in the garden.
This is a madhouse.
Just like at our place.
So, Marcelka, what's going on?
Well, first of all.
You're going to Tibet without me.
And this phone doesn't work, so I had to give the suppliers my mobile number.
And now they're sending me dirty texts.
Well, it probably isn't that bad.
There's a picture attached.
Wow, that one has a beard.
That's not a beard.
Okay, that's bad.
Something has to be done about this phone.
I thought there should be some wire going into it.
No, no, it's wireless.
Then what's this...
This wire going into the wall.
That's the wired radio.
You disconnected the phone.
I had to.
Because of God's Mills.
You have to answer the phone.
But they'll come.
They'll come anyway, you can't escape them.
Stibor Manda hid from them for three months in the Tatras at a sheepfold and they still got him.
They caught him with a sheep.
Bad luck, since Borek is allergic to sheep's wool.
Sure, it's manipulation.
But if you arrange it with them, you can at least prepare.
Besides, it'll be the same guy who's supposed to deliver that Pavarotti for us.
The shop?
Pacovsky here.
Hello, is that you, hello.
Alright, and when will you come?
Excellent, excellent, we'll look forward to it, certainly.
Yes, yes, goodbye.
So when will he deliver it?
That was God's Mills.
They were glad I took it.
They were about to skip me and call Vitek Vavra.
He always came after me.
Dad, don't worry, you'll manage.
Ivushka, don't take this lightly, listen.
Singer Richard Velen was taken to a psychiatric hospital after the broadcast of God's Mills.
The television station issued only a brief statement.
We told you so.
That can't happen to us, though.
Right, if we prepare.
You'll be a successful businessman, Iva a model daughter, and Mr. Ozzak someone who has nothing to do with you.
Say something, bro.
Don't talk to the driver while driving!
But you have to say something.
After all, you're family too.
The last time I was on TV, it was nothing but trouble.
No wonder.
You attacked the Czech national team mascot on live TV.
How was I supposed to know the guy was a mascot?
He was dressed as a lion.
So, same thing.
A tractor is coming from the left.
This red one is a car and there's a truck parked here.
Which goes first?
Think about it logically.
So logically, the dude in the red car will zoom through first, before those two slowpokes even react.
The tractor goes first.
Are you kidding, Iva, have you ever seen a tractor?
The red one is at a stop sign, it goes last.
That stupid stop sign again.
The stop sign is the worst sign of all.
It's responsible for all crashes.
For all your crashes.
Hey, Iva.
Hello, Mr. Ozzak.
So, did you show them?
Yeah, he showed them how to wreck five cars in one go.
Look, that wasn't my fault.
Whoever invented signs wasn't right in the head.
My thoughts exactly.
Probably the same guy who invented left and right.
The instructor says, turn toward Plzen.
I see this sign.
That's obvious, it says it right here.
Twelve percent.
Instead, a crazy hill appears.
Or this one.
We had a red car.
I look and see.
Hooray!
Red cars to the left.
There are nothing but idiots driving toward me.
There's nothing here.
So everything's allowed.
I drive in, and guess what was there?
The police.
They took the instructor's license.
Signs are truly evil.
Not all of them.
Like the brass band prohibition sign.
Great sign.
Uncle, why are you even learning to drive?
The Jezevec is just across the street.
Angry Bee!
My favorite band is looking for a driver.
The Dots are going on tour?
Yeah.
Nobody lets them rehearse, so they play while driving in a van.
The last driver committed suicide.
They need a tough guy as a driver.
And not someone who lets a tractor pass them.
The tractor had the right of way, check the test results.
What?
The results are in there?
Yeah.
Then why have we been studying this for an hour?
Now we need to pull together.
We'll be on TV, but we have a chance to come out with dignity.
I've been thinking about it.
And I don't want to be on it.
Wait, Ivushka, you have to.
You're the daughter, Ozzak doesn't have to.
What do you mean I don't have to?
But I don't want to be on it.
I don't want to be on it either.
Excellent.
But I want my bro to want me to be there.
Fine.
Ozzak, I want you to be there.
No way.
But if Ozzak doesn't have to be there, I won't be there either.
Wait, but not being there won't help you, Ivushka.
Mr. Pacovsky.
Iva, I want to be on TV with you.
Forget it, only family will be there.
So you'll be there?
No way.
But they'll film you going to the bathroom, going to school, working out.
Mr. Pacovsky, I absolutely need to be on TV with you, Budilka Kvasnickova stripped in front of them.
How do we get rid of him?
Mr. Ozzak, I'm practically like your son.
If I ever had a son, it'd be you, Lexa.
Then adopt me.
Jesus, you've lost your mind.
Will you fetch beer?
Sure, gladly.
Go on then, son.
Thanks, Dad.
For God's sake, Uncle, what have you done?
The kid needs a dad.
Enough.
It's none of your business, you're not family.
But I know the media.
And I'm here to tell you what to say.
How about the truth?
What else?
The truth?
Ivushka, truth on television is a thing of the past.
These days it's about setting themes.
Everyone should have their own.
Hold on, nobody told me that.
I've got a theme!
Ozzak, we already agreed that I want you to be there, but you don't want to.
Signs!
I can finally tell the whole world that signs are to blame for all accidents!
Couldn't you say that off the air?
Like at the Jezevec, to someone other than the world?
No, everyone has to hear it.
Signs are evil and the stop sign is the worst of all.
Ozzak, that's nonsense.
Right, only Stefan Babecky can save this, a media expert.
He handled the Temelin explosion.
Marcelka, please.
There was never any explosion at Temelin.
Now you see how good he is.
Next week I won't be able to show my face.
Just give Ozzak the driver's license already.
No, I mean the TV thing.
What's the worst that could happen?
I have nothing to hide.
Look, Tomas, how are you worse off than anyone else in this pub?
Look at me, for example.
You've got Ozzak, I've got Lexa.
One to one.
You've got Iva, I've got Sasha.
You're ahead.
Stefan is very sorry, but he had to rush to Dukovany because nothing happened there.
But I have the materials he prepared for you.
So let's go through this quickly and then study up.
Where's Ozzak?
He has driving lessons, but he'll come.
I've followed my father's musical career with respect and I'm a big fan of his.
Thanks, sweetie.
Everyone's going to make fun of me.
Why?
It actually sounds nice when you say it.
Hey, you know that according to my file you want to be a teacher?
And supposedly cooking and sex education?
But Ivushka, it says music and history.
It's decent.
Like this little outfit.
I had it made for you for the TV appearance.
And where?
At a burlap sack factory?
This is exactly what Stefan warned me about.
Speaking freely.
That's exactly what they're waiting for.
A little sentence like that, they cut a piece of it and make it a headline.
They have the technology.
You say "library, skid" and they make you sound vulgar.
Well then all these editors are total crap.
They can twist anything this way.
Like here.
In the hundred meter dash, I improved by four seconds.
Huh?
It should have said seconds there.
Marcelka, she has a point.
If they can really change everything we say.
For God's sake, is it so hard to think twice before blurting something out?
I killed her.
What?
This is exactly what I was talking about.
It's over.
Oh God, what happened?
Stefan, which lawyer does your contracts?
Nothing will help.
I'm a murderer.
Or maybe just...
Two, seven, eight.
Thanks, Steffy.
Are you still in Dukovany?
What do you mean they don't exist?
We were just there the other day.
I'll never forget the sight.
Those wide-open eyes.
That beak open in a scream.
Wings as if begging for help.
Wait, wings, beak.
What did he run over?
Rest in peace.
I promise you a dignified funeral.
And you'll have a beautiful coffin.
It's all because of those damn traffic signs.
I took it down, you know, so it wouldn't confuse anyone else.
It said cows.
I'm driving along, looking for cows, and...
Whoever put it there has your blood on their hands, you know?
I promise you, my friend, you're the last.
I swear right here that I'll avenge you.
So, no more victims.
Hi, Dad.
Come here, son.
Pay your respects to Divis here.
A martyr of the rules of the road.
Divis?
That's a nice name for a chicken.
I named him after the expression he had when we met.
A report from the studio, Pavel.
And who will we extinguish next?
Tomas Pacovsky.
Probably only those of you who take ginkgo daily remember him.
But you know his brother, his delightful little daughter.
Watch God's Mills exactly one week from now.
I'll scratch his eyes out.
No, no, don't let them provoke you, Ivushka, please.
That's exactly what they're waiting for.
I'll tell them everything, they won't need to edit a thing, this just can't be.
Domestic news.
A gang of sign thieves is wreaking havoc in the city and has completely paralyzed traffic.
Chaos reigns in the city, people are afraid.
Ivushka, I wanted to ask, why is there a no-entry sign in our bathroom?
Ozzak?
There is now total chaos on the main highway.
That's weird, we already fixed that one.
Ozzak.
I didn't leave a single one.
Don't worry, Daddy.
What is this supposed to mean?
No more traffic accidents.
You have to put those signs back immediately.
The locations of the stolen signs are being guarded by police in case the criminals return to the scene.
You'll stay home.
Of course I will.
We did what we had to.
Right.
Divis's fate will not be repeated.
Who the hell is Divis?
Who is Divis?
Divis is...
Gone!
What, you mean the dead chicken?
Don't talk about him like that.
Are you going to tell me you ate him?
The pan was empty when I got home.
How could we not have heard that?
As if someone tapped.
A miracle.
She was just stunned.
It's a miracle.
It's a reward for the fight against signs.
Ozzak, that chicken is leaving this house.
Are you crazy?
Now you want to send him back into that jungle when you saw what's on TV?
Accidents everywhere.
What are you going to do, teach traffic signs to a chicken?
So what?
It wouldn't be the first chicken with a driver's license.
Nobody can find out about this.
We've set up a traffic playground for you.
Marcelka, has Stefan come back from Dukovany yet?
What?
He was never there?
Stefan figured out how to save everything.
It's a scenario for the most critical situations.
Did he use it at Dukovany?
Where?
Tomas, let's not kid ourselves.
Iva and Ozzak are very nice people, but there's no way to film with them.
So what do we do?
Look at those two over there.
They're professionals from an extras agency.
They'll play Iva and Ozzak.
As in I'd deny Iva?
And Ozzak.
Never.
I arranged the TV thing for tomorrow.
Iva and Mr. Ozzak will be doing their driving exams, so they won't be home.
And instead of them?
These lovely people can fill in.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're one family and we'll manage.
I'll keep Ozzak in line.
I'll transform the family into a noble one.
Excuse me, I'm Pacovsky, you must be my brother, right?
Yes, Daniel Hrachovsky.
Daniel.
The TV people will be thrilled.
A sharp guy, hair slicked back.
Divis, come on, you need to eat something.
We have an exam coming up.
Wait, you're taking the chicken with you?
He claims it'll whisper answers to him.
That it knows signs better than he does.
Which is true.
With Divis, we'll pull through, you know?
And then, Angry Bee, we'll fly off into the world.
Anyway, aren't you going to be late?
Why are you rushing us?
Oh no, no, take it easy, so they don't leave without you.
And Divis looks like he's ready to go too.
You already put back those stolen signs, right?
Sure.
To the same spots, the same signs?
To the same spots, definitely.
Sure.
Let's go then.
Break a leg, break a leg, break a leg.
I'll keep my fingers crossed.
Welcome to the new Pacovskys.
I work in your shop, do the accounting, and help raise your daughter.
Your hobbies?
Yachting, golf, and caring for the terminally ill.
And my brother Tomas's music.
You don't have to.
But I genuinely like it.
I listened to it yesterday and I've been humming it all morning.
Let's hope Miss Eva is just as good.
Three mojitos, an American lemonade for me, and a coffee for Dad.
Two sugars and lots of milk, just the way you like it.
How much do they charge per hour?
Why?
I was thinking I'd borrow them for the occasional weekend.
Safe travels.
Thank you very much.
Wow, you were excellent.
Daniel, when you talked about caring for the dying in the hospice and started crying.
I swear, I actually believed you.
I used the Stanislavsky method.
Emotional recall.
My turtle recently died.
So that's why you were talking about their last little lettuce leaves?
Exactly.
And when Miss Eva talked about that sad look of the little dog without a leg, I nearly cried myself.
Also emotional recall?
Yes, my dachshund was hit by a bus.
Of course.
Why don't we go have lunch together?
I'm sorry, but at three I'm playing a lady's college-age son.
I need to prepare.
Of course.
It was an honor being your brother.
Thank you, thank you so much, thank you.
Thank you too, so much, thank you.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye.
The crew was thrilled.
They said they'd never filmed such an ideal family.
It's rather empty in here.
Iva and Ozzak will be here soon.
Exactly.
Father, I told you I don't give a damn about that TV circus.
You know about the filming?
Their car is parked out front, kind of hard to miss.
Don't worry, Ivushka, nobody's going to film you.
So it'll be without me?
Great.
See, Tomas, and you said Miss Evicka would bother Iva.
Who is Miss Evicka?
Oh, you haven't told her yet.
Never mind, I'll go.
Can I come with you?
Not until you tell me who Miss Evicka is.
I was trying to protect you from the media filth.
You yourself said you didn't want to be on TV.
So I talked to Marcelka and...
Actually, Marcelka hired stand-ins.
What?
Like a replacement daughter.
You can't be serious.
You hired a stranger to play me, are you ashamed of me?
I'm not, Ivushka.
Then call them right now and tell them they can't air it.
But that'll really make them angry.
And what am I supposed to tell them?
That you lied and cheated.
But that's exactly what they want to hear.
Then you'll make them happy.
Jesus, what a situation.
If my bro were here, he'd figure something out.
Ozzak?
No, I mean Daniel.
I almost passed the test and then the cameraman got in my way.
Jesus Mary.
Our recorded footage.
Divis didn't warn me.
Oh God, is he okay?
Oh yeah, she's a chicken of steel, she can take it.
But the cameraman.
He's worse off.
So nothing will come of this whole thing?
Well, maybe the footage could still be salvaged.
Great, see, which bro will save you in the end.
I'd still like to know if Divis will ever come back.
Don't get your hopes up, whoever stole that car took Divis, killed him, and roasted him.
Maybe Divis drove off on his own.
For God's sake, bro, a chicken can't drive a car.
Divis is a pro.
Turn on the TV, quick.
Hurry.
We recorded an exclusive interview with the leader of the sign-stealing gang, but we promised not to reveal his identity.
Hey, I'm Lexa.
I say hi to Mom and everyone at the Jezevec.
Why did you do it?
Because signs cause traffic accidents.
Away with them.
And I salute the real boss.
You know who you are, Dad.
Respect!
Well, if he wanted to be on TV, that kid will be somebody someday.
A chip off the old block.
I'll smack him just in case, but it won't help.
Still better than if we'd been on TV ourselves.
Cash out!
Pacovsky?
Ah, it's you, excellent.
And when are you coming?
Great, we'll look forward to it.
Yes, yes.
Alright, goodbye then.
That was Daniel and Evicka.
They're coming for Sunday lunch.
This is unbearable!