https://slama.dev/comeback/
Where are you going?
I said something, didn't I?
But Dad, everyone's going.
These kinds of protests are dangerous.
But this is a peaceful protest against fascism.
How peaceful?
Well, we'll just peacefully express our opinion, calmly.
Well, you can express it calmly right here in your room, can't you?
I'll have an escort.
You don't have to worry about me at all.
Anarchy!
Who's covering for the Nazis?
It's the police!
Nicely, Mr. Pacovsky.
Hi, Lexa.
What's in that backpack?
Dice.
He beat me again, Iva.
So peacefully?
Right here in your room, kiddo.
Moron.
Ozzak, what about that door?
We clearly agreed you'd fix it this morning.
Is it necessary?
It is necessary, it keeps getting stuck, see.
Last time I almost spent the whole night here with Marcelka.
Oh damn, this is where the fun ends.
I'm on it.
Watch, click it twice.
Three strokes.
And then...
And done.
Can I help you?
Hello, I'm looking for...
Oh, you have Tokyo Dracula.
Good eye, young man.
And good taste.
That's a solid piece of merch.
But I've got a guy who imports it from Japan.
That must cost a fortune.
See, bro, you said nobody would appreciate it.
No, I said nobody would buy it, that's different.
Shall I ring it up?
You must be doing pretty well if you can afford to order such rarities, huh?
Well, can't complain.
You can't.
That's a different situation now.
Wait, wait.
Think I scared him off with the ringing up?
This is a holdup.
Wait.
Look, don't take it personally, kid, but I'm going for lunch.
No wait, you can't.
I can't? I have to, I'm hungry.
Back it up.
And hands up, Ozzak.
I can't send you anywhere alone.
When you rob a store, you can't let people leave.
Nobody stays here long anyway.
And you shut up too.
Understand that these things are important, if everyone just sat at home, then...
Yeah, but your dad forbade it.
He can't forbid me from expressing my opinion.
No, but he can forbid you from going outside.
But I can hardly express my opinion at home.
That's true.
And when I do express it, nothing comes of it anyway.
Right.
I'm interested in your opinion, for example.
I just mean, you're grounded.
And that has to stop too.
Every time he doesn't know what to say, he grounds me.
I'm going to have it out with him.
Lexa, is it me or do you suddenly look better?
Well, if you noticed, it's the balaclava.
I got it for you.
Not bad.
Better than I thought.
What kind of business did you pick?
There's 50 crowns in the register and an Arakain badge.
I forgot it there.
So, bro, what's the plan?
I have a plan?
In these situations someone always has a plan.
I don't have one, so you must.
I have a plan.
I'll wait till they leave.
But they're taking all our CDs meanwhile.
If it was some pop idiot, I wouldn't care, but this one's got taste.
He's going to pick out my best stuff.
Sorry, miss, we're closed.
Are you from social services?
We're closed.
Run, boy!
Run away!
And take the salami and that Led Zeppelin collection too!
It's hidden behind the Czech pop from the eighties!
But you said someone stole those Zeppelins.
They cost me two thousand without markup.
I hid them.
I was afraid someone would buy them.
Sit down.
Now this is really too much.
You're going to tie me up every time I want to go out?
No, just when we get robbed.
Yeah, we got robbed.
What do they want to steal?
Nirvana CDs?
Christ, don't give them ideas.
We have to hang in there.
Maybe they'll leave soon.
Then I might still make the protest.
Absolutely not, don't even think about it.
Only over my dead body.
You hired them so I can't go anywhere.
Am I crazy?
Got a plan yet?
Well, Marcelka comes back from the dentist at eleven, maybe she'll sort it out.
How?
I don't know, but Marcelka has a tendency to sort things out.
Great.
Wait.
I'm actually looking forward to Marcelka coming.
Tomas?
We're not going to rob this stupid store.
Can't you lock a door?
Marcelka!
Run away!
Call the police!
Let me go!
Come here!
Grab that creature!
Sit down!
We're screwed.
Lexa will probably come looking for me.
Definitely screwed.
What are you taking off?
We're leaving soon anyway.
It's really itchy.
You have to get used to it.
There'll be cops there.
Iva's been in there quite a while.
Maybe that Mr. Pacovsky locked her in.
He's a real tyrant.
I'll go check it out.
I'll be right back.
Meanwhile, keep rolling the dice.
Practice up.
Occupied!
We're already here!
Sure.
See you then.
Anarchy!
We expected more from you.
No, I'm really scared.
Why are they taking so long?
They grab the cash from the register and go, right?
They're probably looking for a safe.
Well, that'll take a while.
We don't even have a safe.
Or do we?
See, you keep blaming me for not selling anything, and look how handy that is now.
Thanks for reminding me of our pitiful financial situation at this moment.
Dad, please, could you focus on what's actually important for a minute?
My reserve beer.
Well, that would be a tragedy.
Jesus, you take it out too.
No, I'm enjoying the quiet.
Whoa, there are some protesters in the store.
Think they're Iva's friends?
I don't know, you should ask her.
She wasn't there.
And Mr. Pacovsky?
Not either.
And Mr. Ozzak?
No.
And Mrs. Marcelka?
Just the two protesters.
Doesn't that seem weird to you?
No.
Although maybe Mr. Pacovsky is also a fascist, that would explain why he wouldn't let Iva go.
Lexa, or maybe those aren't protesters but robbers.
Damn.
I'm calling the police.
Good idea.
At least there'll be fewer at the protest.
Hello, this is Sasa.
I'd like to report a crime.
At the store Two Chords, Horakova 11, there's no Mr. Pacovsky, no Mr. Ozzak, and no Mrs. Marcelka.
And there are two robbers in there.
What, I'm not joking?
You're an amateur.
Bomb, tell them there's a bomb.
Careful, there's a bomb.
Wonderful.
Lex, how'd you come up with that?
Totally by accident.
It was just like before a math test.
I'm going crazy.
First you can't close the door properly and now you can't open it.
You know, it was always fix that door, fix that door.
And now it's handy that it won't open?
I'd prefer it if they finally got out.
Maybe I want to say something important.
Nail file, back pocket.
And she said important.
Our lives are at stake, well the Zeppelins, and this one's thinking about nails.
Uncle, Marcelka probably meant we could cut through the ropes.
Ivuska, you're a genius.
And what about me?
You get the nail file out.
Hard to do with my hands tied.
You'll have to reach in for me.
Where?
In the back pocket for the nail file.
I'm supposed to touch your butt?
You have something against my butt?
No, but I don't have anything for it either.
You brute!
Ozzak, behave yourself and touch Marcelka's butt.
Forget it.
He's not touching my butt.
I'll find someone else.
Stop that.
Fine.
It's something else, it's something else.
It's a cold twelve-pack.
It's a cold...
I got it.
Are you satisfied?
No, we're not satisfied.
Well then, what else would you like?
For you to take the nail file out of my pocket.
Oh right.
Again.
Here you go.
You, you're coming with me.
I told you to grab something valuable if they don't have money.
It's hard for an independent music store to make money.
Are you crazy, woman?
This is the best thing we've got here.
Fine.
Then wrap it up.
No, not this one.
Otherwise take anything you want.
Even my reserve beer behind the counter.
Yeah.
Okay, you've got the beer, now give me the record back.
I make the rules here.
And you're going to tell me why the door won't open.
Oh, the door won't open, it won't open for anyone who doesn't know the special trick.
Then you better tell me that trick.
Ha, you can torture me, I won't say a word.
As you wish.
There's too much fat on that.
Hand me the record.
Please.
Fair terrorists release women, children, and rock LPs first.
We're not fair.
Enough, stop it.
Will you tell me your trick?
I didn't say that.
I wanted you to stop.
Fine, I'm counting to three.
And then this kid tells me your best record.
You're not even human.
Ozzak, open that door right now.
We're not going to negotiate with them.
Next month you get all shifts with Marcelka.
I'll tell you everything.
Dude, untie me.
Smoke on the Water.
Oh damn.
What's happening?
Last time it popped like that, the fire department had to come.
Please, get him out of here, I'm scared.
I'll find a wrench and we'll get out.
Wait.
But I always have all shifts with Marcelka.
Hey, I wanted to ask you something.
If you'd go out tonight?
What?
Like, after your mom finishes robbing my dad's store?
Well, professional and private life shouldn't mix.
I heard you're going to the protest.
I wanted to too, but my mom wouldn't let me.
Your mother is a sensible woman.
As long as she's not robbing stores.
What are you doing Thursday evening?
Would you go...
Absolutely not.
The only place you two are going together is court.
You as the defendant and her as the witness.
Wait, we have a lot in common.
Like, we both have parents who restrict us.
Yes, Mom isn't bad.
She tells us that protests won't pay the bills.
That nothing beats a good break-in.
We've got that in common.
Maybe we really should go out sometime and talk about it.
Wait a second.
Ivuska, now he tied you up.
What do you mean wait?
Tied up in a closet or grounded in an apartment, it's the same in the end, right?
So should I go for it?
This is how all my dates end.
Good lord.
Brats outside and you're in here flirting.
Mom, we're here...
This girl is not for you.
Told you.
A sensible woman.
You deserve someone better.
How better?
What do you mean better?
When your moron can't even rob their store.
Your store can't be robbed.
That's against the laws of nature.
Get up.
That must be them.
Excuse me.
Good day.
I'm a psychologist from the organized crime unit of the Czech Republic police.
That's commendable work.
The police commit loads of crimes.
Well, no.
The police investigate crimes.
It's a vicious circle.
The bomb thing, that was me.
Lock me up.
No, I'm not an investigator, I'm a psychologist, a specialist in delivering bad news to relatives of crime victims.
I'm here to gently tell Miss Iva Pacovska that her father and uncle are in mortal danger.
What?
My God, it's you.
I mumbled it, sorry, this is my first assignment and I'm terribly sorry.
You hug?
Yes, I'm trained for it.
We have to provide all assistance to relatives of victims.
All assistance?
This is just a neighbor.
I'm the one who needs help here.
Are you Iva Pacovska?
I'm the son.
Ivan.
You must have an error there.
This would happen to me.
But you're not...
Go away, you random neighbor!
Daddy, Uncle.
I think I could use a little hug.
What got into you?
Miss, it would really be better if you left, because Ivan here.
Needs professional care.
Fine, I'll wait outside the door.
Don't let anyone in!
I couldn't bear the press attention.
You know, sometimes the world seems so cruel to me.
I'll support you.
Then I'll lean on you, if you don't mind.
Come on, pick up.
Who is it?
Who do you think?
Police.
You're going to negotiate now.
They don't have you in the voice database.
Hello?
What?
No!
Are you crazy?
I said you should negotiate.
No, that was some kid from the neighbors.
He asked if we could drag out the robbery as long as possible.
Hello?
Yes?
What, our demands?
Well, I don't know, just free us.
I'm sorry?
Right, their demands.
Do you have any demands?
Hang on, they're looking for them.
Yeah, got it, I'll read.
So...
A car with a full tank.
With a turbo.
A plane at Ruzyne airport, GPS navigation, a manual on how to fly a plane, and a month's supply of food.
And peanut butter.
Yeah, I'll pass it on.
Listen, they want one hostage for each item.
So that's a car, GPS navigation, a month's supply of food, peanut butter.
The plane.
Five.
Damn.
We need one more.
Know anyone?
Maybe from the neighborhood?
We have four, we'll give four.
Fine.
Listen, they say only four.
Yeah, I'll pass it on.
Listen, according to some EU directive they shouldn't even be talking to you, right?
So five or nothing.
Then drop the peanut butter.
Yeah, that's reasonable.
Well, Mom.
Can't we drop the plane instead?
That's non-negotiable.
Go get them.
Sure.
Hey, so in the end, drop the peanut butter.
Fine.
All right, we're done here, mama.
I'm done with this.
Sorry, Mom, I got distracted.
So nobody do anything stupid.
Let my dad go.
Or what?
Or...
Or we'll give your boy a buzz cut.
Mom, don't be crazy.
What if they actually pull the trigger?
You think I put bullets in it?
According to specialist literature, hug therapy works mostly on children under five.
Is it really helping you?
I'd like more.
But ten minutes maximum.
Otherwise the maternal fixation will be disrupted.
No risk of that with me.
Thanks.
You're really helping me here, this is my first assignment, and a hostage situation on top of it.
You're wonderful.
I'll write a thank-you note to the commander.
That would really help me.
How about that hug therapy?
Can we increase the dose a bit?
Please.
So you never trusted me.
I did, but I wasn't completely sure.
And what if things went wrong?
Things always went wrong because of you.
And I was there to protect you.
But I'm old enough to protect myself, if you'd let me.
I want to make you proud, Mom.
Proud?
You know what would make me proud? If you were a proper criminal.
You know, projecting your own ambitions onto children is often a source of problems.
Well yeah, actually the kid's not that bad.
I was actually scared of him for a moment, if only you didn't keep nagging him.
Iva, how dare you talk like that?
I understand you, you mean well, but the kid doesn't get it yet.
She can't mean well when she keeps hassling him like this.
The kid ends up totally crushed.
So let him try something on his own.
Well, it doesn't have to be anything big.
Maybe just a newsstand, or some old lady.
Have you lost your mind?
Not completely alone.
I think it'd be more than enough if you just followed him discreetly from a distance.
I never wanted to do this job anyway.
So you'd rather go to that math and physics school?
Yeah.
Skin-to-skin therapy is recommended for severe hypothermia.
Dear Iva, in the end everything turned out fine.
It turned out the judge also lived with his parents for a long time.
Mom got five years, but she seems happy there because she only calls me once a month.
Although maybe that's because she's only allowed one phone call a month.
Well, nice letter.
Except you could've just mailed it.
I wanted to see you again.
Well, you're old enough, decide what you want.
Dad, that's great, thanks.
So no.
I probably won't have time for about a year anyway.
We have to go.
We have maternal detachment therapy.
Goodbye.
I'm proud of you.
Why?
Well, how you peacefully expressed your views on a social issue at that protest.
I'm glad you let me go in the end.
You were right.
It was peaceful.
So you didn't even have to come with me in the end.
Good?
Excellent.
Aren't you cold?
Yeah.
Yeah?