https://slama.dev/comeback/
Good afternoon.
Hello.
I'm looking for Mr. Pacovsky.
That's me.
I have something for you here.
Right, please sign here for me.
Thanks.
Have a nice day.
Leather on...
Yeah, I'm coming.
Yeah, one moment.
Yeah.
Tomas, hold on.
Try to stay conscious.
What's happening?
Do you need any help?
What happened?
Ambulance.
He needs a doctor.
Horakova 11.
Tomas, hold on.
A man.
About 40 years old.
Yes, he's conscious.
He's standing.
He's standing by the wall holding ketchup.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I'm canceling the order.
What happened?
I thought you'd been shot.
By whom?
Zoran.
We were robbed, but they didn't take any money.
How much did we have?
Nothing, as usual.
So what did they want?
I don't know, I got punched and then had to sign for a delivery.
That was Zoran.
Who's Zoran?
My husband.
Your old man hit a messenger?
No, a publisher.
And why would he hit you, Ozzak?
Zoran is a southerner, hot-headed.
He acts first and thinks later.
He's also a bit jealous right now.
No husband punched me, a messenger did.
Zoran is swamped with work.
He publishes all the color magazines in the country.
He can't be in ten places at once.
He uses messengers all the time.
Marcelka, why is Zoran beating up Ozzak?
He's actually beating up you.
I may have mentioned you inappropriately at home.
He's so wonderful, attentive, sensitive.
He really listens when I talk to him.
I'm so happy.
Thank you for letting me come back to work.
He's terribly jealous.
Hey.
And why do I have to fight a messenger because of that?
Zoran is a media mogul.
It's practically impossible to meet him in person.
He even sent me the engagement ring by courier.
And the guy even recited Macha to me along with it.
In Croatian.
It was a late night.
First of May.
Evening in May.
It was the time for love.
The turtledove's call to love sang out.
The pine forest's fragrance.
Smelled wonderful, it was so romantic.
Most importantly, nothing happened.
He was simply in the wrong place at the wrong time.
Hi, I'm Marek Vasut, president of the Studs.
As you surely know, in the last eight seasons of Hitting On Women I've always been crowned king of the hunt.
Now explain one thing to me.
What exactly do you expect from this DVD?
By buying it, you're only proving one single thing.
That you're an absolute zero and a total loser.
So turn this off nicely now and go back to your post-pubescent wet dreams.
OK?
Good night.
You didn't turn it off.
You held out.
Well, maybe something will come of you after all.
Thanks, Marek.
You've already grasped rule number one.
When it comes to sex,
someone always tries to talk you out of it.
But no.
Let's just stay friends.
Or don't even come near me with that clown act, buddy.
Or even...
Me?
Cut it out.
He just told me he'd take me to Liberec, Mr. Vasut.
It's all just talk.
Why are you wasting money on such nonsense?
It says here.
96% success rate.
Pick up anyone, anytime, anywhere.
There's even a warranty.
Look, money-back guarantee in case of failure.
This is awesome, babe.
Wow.
Do you think it would work on her?
You still haven't given up.
Fine, I'll give it one more try with you.
I'll reveal the king of the hunt's secret.
A man's body speaks for him.
Body language.
The whole miracle is called melons and caraway seeds.
Watch.
I walk up to a babe, turn like this, and show two melons.
The other one.
And she's already getting hot under the collar.
Then I slowly turn, wiggle my butt, she sees two caraway seeds, and she's mine.
Piece of cake.
You look like a ballet dancer.
And what would you do?
You have to throw a woman off guard, surprise her.
Do something unusual, otherwise she won't go for it.
And that's it?
That'll just amuse her, make her laugh.
And then you have to surprise her.
Like how, for instance.
Well, that doesn't work on me.
Because you're not a woman.
And Marcelka, how about your Othello?
There won't be any more deliveries.
Too bad, I was starting to get used to it.
What was lying on his desk?
Marcelka, there are worse magazines in the world.
Like Bravicko, for example.
Bravicko is fine.
It was lying there alive.
And without any clothes.
Meaning she was completely naked?
Yeah.
The only thing she was wearing was Zoran.
Didn't you mean to say a bathrobe?
No.
It was just Zoran.
His brother is in Croatia.
Well, Marcelka, it's surely some kind of misunderstanding.
Good day.
Tears of love, when they fall, you won't return, I in my heart...
Enough, this recitation won't move me anymore.
Who does he think he is?
That he'll send another apology by mail?
That he'll fix things with this broom?
Wait, I need to bring a reply.
Dear Zoran, I've had enough of this long-distance marriage.
Goodnight texts, phone sex, and breakfasts alone.
I've had enough of your lies about loving me and empty promises about children.
You can't make me a baby through a messenger, Zoran.
You find time for a floozy like that, Zoran.
And I'm supposed to settle for a messenger instead of you?
That's pretty pathetic, Zoran.
It is pathetic, you have to admit.
Well, it doesn't really concern me, so...
Anyway.
It's pathetic, Zoran, and I am filing for divorce.
Is that all?
No, this too.
Right, thank you.
Please just sign here for me.
Your message will be delivered tomorrow morning by 8 AM.
You can of course track the shipment online as well.
With us, you're faster than the competition.
Have a nice day.
Say what you want, but that guy is a pro.
Oh look.
Who's crawling back again.
Your buddy's tricks didn't work, huh?
So back to proven quality.
The very first time you talk to a woman, she has to know that only with you will she experience what she's been waiting for her whole fifteen years.
Hi, I'm Marek Vasut.
How about we take a trip to Liberec.
Ozzak!
Ozzak, go open the door.
Who is it?
A bogeyman.
Police?
Yeah.
They found some squatters.
But they're already gone.
We don't want any squatters.
Thanks, this isn't a shelter.
Stop messing around and open up.
No.
What is it?
I don't know, Ozzak won't open the door again.
So who is it?
A bogeyman.
It would only be for a few days.
Until I pull myself together a bit, get myself sorted, recharge.
Of course, Marcelka, you can stay as long as you want.
Until you pull yourself together.
I won't be a bother.
Marcelka, do you happen to know where the things from my room went?
I moved them to Ozzak's room.
Why?
You can't keep sleeping on the little couch, Tomas.
Who swapped my things for colored ones?
It's Saturday.
I did laundry.
What's an exercise bike doing in my room?
I took the liberty, you know, because of your problem areas.
The only problem area around here is her.
We need ten kilos of flour for this.
She increased the resistance on me again.
I'm not touching that vacuum cleaner.
Yeah.
Good afternoon.
Hi.
Is Iva home?
Well, if only.
It's three thirty, she's doing homework until five twenty, then she exercises on the bike.
Could you take it for me?
Knead my dough!
Iva has free time, Ozzak is in his room.
Did he die?
No.
Wow, it's really different around here.
Sasa, you didn't change your shoes?
Ozzak will kill you.
Iva, I don't even recognize you.
For real.
What's happened to us?
We can't just kick her out.
She said until she pulls herself together.
So let her pull herself together and go.
Ozzak, why are you bringing the chore schedule into this?
Yeah, the stairs and stroller room already keep me busy without it.
So, it's clear that Mamba has to go.
But gently.
Nothing gentle.
Mamba.
Husband.
Mistress.
Us.
Got it?
I see.
So for clarity, once more.
Mamba.
Zoran.
The one with the boobs, and O.
What's O?
Ozzak.
And no Mamba is going to push him around.
Push around!
I have laundry in the machine.
Hi, I'm Vasut.
What, what are you doing?
Caraway seeds and melons.
He's on some kind of pills.
I told you, like this.
Here we go again.
So, back to business.
Mamba's with us because she's not with Zoran, because Zoran is with that woman.
So, what do you suggest?
Isn't that a bit much?
You think?
Maybe it would be enough if someone talked to her reasonably.
Or what if we found a lover for the mistress?
What?
If we found a lover for the mistress, Zoran couldn't be with the mistress because she'd have a lover, and he'd come back to Marcelka.
I mean, to Mamba.
But isn't that a bit too complicated?
Wait, that actually makes sense.
If we found a lover for the busty one, then Zoran would come back to Marcelka.
We need a lover.
So who's volunteering?
Don't count on me.
Definitely not me either.
So nobody.
Are you afraid of Zoran, Strida?
I'm not afraid of anything or anyone.
Watch out, messenger!
Those are baby monitors!
Lexa, quit it.
You could never even pack a sleeping bag.
I don't want to pick up girls.
I have a proposal.
Hi, Strida.
Strida?
Only one little girl was ever allowed to call me Strida.
And that's you, Ivuska.
You're a woman now?
How old are you?
Thirteen.
You don't look it.
Strida, I need an expert on women.
I'd love to, but you'll have to wait two years.
Then maybe I'll take you to Liberec.
Not me, not me.
Her.
You're on?
Well now, that's a challenge.
Good afternoon, I have a delivery here.
Who'll sign for it?
Ozzy Osbourne, best of, limited edition.
That's for me.
I figured.
Right, sign here please.
Thanks.
By the way.
I have something else for you.
What?
There's a message for the recipient.
Hands off my woman.
Well, that was probably for me.
We'll sort this out between us.
Have a nice day.
What the hell kind of day is this?
Everything was going smoothly.
Eye contact, a spark.
Introductions, she fainted.
Knee contact, awesome.
And then that ninja barges in.
The messenger.
Yeah, I know.
And he had a baseball bat.
Zoran is escalating.
Poor Strida.
Mr. Vasut, I can see you're weakened, that you can't defend yourself, but I'd still like you to give me my money back.
What kind of nutjob is this?
Melons and caraway seeds don't work, I looked like an idiot.
I have a right to a refund.
It says so right here.
Did you read it properly, kid?
You probably don't know.
Because otherwise you'd see that clause 17B... I'm saying...
I can't see a damn thing either, it's all that fine print I've been reading.
In the event that you are an idiot, the warranty does not apply to you.
I didn't notice that.
My mistake.
It can be fixed.
You can buy the DVD "Reading Contracts with Marek Vasut."
Here we have one Vienna coffee, one Pilsner, and four Bozkovs.
But I wanted an espresso.
You just said your future is being decided.
Should I take it back?
That's what I thought.
You're adorably nervous, Tomas.
You know, Marcelka, I've never been good at saying these things.
Don't thank me, Tomas, I'm happy to do it.
But changes have happened, right?
Yes.
It'll be even better if we don't let up.
Ozzak is getting up pretty well in the mornings now, right?
That's mainly because he sneaks out of morning exercises at the shop.
He won't escape that.
I bought an exercise bike for the shop too.
Tomas, your English, we need to do something about that.
Have you told her yet?
Well, I'm slowly getting to it.
So you'll be bugging me here for another month?
No way.
Look, I want to tell you to move out, OK?
Go on, presto, yesterday was already too late.
See? That didn't even hurt.
Who is this?
Marek Vasut, president of the Studs.
Ozzak, metal god.
So daddy was being sensitive.
What, is she staying?
No, she's leaving.
So what's the problem?
Victory!
But she was really hurt.
Hey Marek, what happened to you?
You wouldn't believe it, kid.
I wanted to thank you.
You helped me when I was at my lowest.
And you gave me shelter.
Until I felt better.
Well, I don't feel better, I feel absolutely terrible.
But I can't stay where I'm not welcome.
I wanted to give your life direction, order, and shape to your problem areas, Ivuska.
I meant well, but you...
Marcelka, wait.
Bro!
You can't leave like this.
I can and I must.
I have somewhere to go.
That was a close one.
Good morning, Marcelka.
It's almost nine.
I only have two hands.
Telekram was always known for opening right on time.
Yes, exactly one hour after he woke up.
We'll open on time if you don't hold me up.
You can pick up that blanket in the meantime.
That is, if it wouldn't bother you.
You can handle it.
That's mine.
Good morning, synthetics.
Marcela.
Zoran.
Are you alone?
Completely.
Unusual.
Marcela, love, I'm a dirty man, but it's all that southern temperament of mine.
That hot, Croatian blood.
You know, my father was also like that, and my grandfather even worse.
I curse myself, I curse them, I curse my big mouth.
Marcela, come back to me.
Zoran, I know you're hot-tempered and you don't mean it, but sometimes I just don't have the energy for you.
I try, I try stubbornly, I swear.
And the one you saw there, she's gone.
She means nothing to me now.
But when you are away from me, I am also alone.
And I cry, cry, like a little chick.
Like a little boy.
Marcela, without you my heart will break.
Little brother.
You have to be nice to me.
Darling!
Zoran, I love you.
I love you too, maximally.
Excuse me, I have to go.
Tomas, can I take today off?
How about the whole week.
That's not enough.
I'll be back tomorrow.
I have a few ideas on how to improve things here.
I also have an idea.
Where are my things?
No problem, I'll send the messenger.
No, we'll send them to you.
What is it?
I'm a dead man.
Your method works.
Which one?
Lexa, I'll wait for you next door in the lingerie boutique.
One more thing.
That was a coincidence.
What should I do?
Take time off school and go for it while luck is dumb.
But wait, Zoran went back to Marcelka.
Well, that's great.
Marek, I need help with a bra.
Don't you want anything from me?
Actually...
Why not?