https://slama.dev/comeback/
You're not having those pickled sausages?
I'm not really in the mood for breakfast.
Feeling sick from that tasting, huh?
Give me a break.
Last night Ziza and I went fishing.
I must've overeaten.
I hope you didn't dig up all the super's tulips again looking for worms.
We were fishing with dough bait.
Did you catch anything?
No.
Then what did you overeat on?
The dough bait.
Have some yogurt.
No, really, will it make you feel better?
Ivuska, I don't know.
Last time I scarfed down a snowman and felt even worse.
And then the guy with the ladder yelled at me.
That wasn't yogurt, that was Primalex paint.
Is there a difference?
Yes, try it.
Plus, if you're lucky, you might find a gold coin.
Where?
In the yogurt.
It's a contest from the dairy companies.
So they can raise the price of dairy products.
Plus they wrote that there's no gold coin in any yogurt.
What a scam.
Alright then, show me what you got, yogurt.
Bro?
He's got the gold coin stuck in his throat.
What?
Don't swallow it!
The Primalex was better.
So let's summarize.
Ozzak swallowed a gold coin with the portrait of Tomas Garik Masaryk worth 20 thousand crowns.
What do we do?
What do you mean, what do we do?
We can't just leave twenty grand in his stomach.
For God's sake, just like normal when someone swallows something.
We simply wait.
Even though this thing is too valuable for us to just let things take their course.
Wait, where do you think you're going?
To the pub, where else.
Absolutely not.
At most you need to go to work.
Actually, you don't need to go to work.
No, nowhere.
From now on we go everywhere together.
Like, everywhere?
Especially there.
Now you're really going overboard, aren't you?
I'm not leaving twenty thousand crowns unsupervised.
Wait, you're gonna go everywhere with me now?
Yes, until the thing comes out.
Fine, that works.
I'll call Metlos that for tonight's ferret neutering we'll need an extra pair of gloves.
Hey.
Simona, what are you doing here?
Ozzak isn't here.
He went to the restroom.
I see, and Tomas?
He went with him.
Oh.
Well, to each their own.
What did you need?
Some advice.
Couldn't I help you with that?
Maybe.
I'd like to meet someone and I'm wondering if there's a catch in this ad.
Lonely, seriously ill eighty-year-old, medical records available for viewing, doctors give him one year at most.
Seeking partner with presentable appearance, refined manners, and knowledge of Esperanto.
Reference: No Heir.
Sounds suspiciously good, right?
Are you serious?
So there is a catch.
It's this Esperanto thing, right?
I figured right away it'd be something dirty.
But Esperanto is a language.
So it is something dirty.
No, it's a language that people speak.
And what do they say?
What do they say?
Everything.
Gross.
Simona, calm down.
Esperanto is a language just like Czech or English.
Well, what really strikes me is his age.
Yeah.
You think he's making himself older?
Well, if he turns out to be some well-maintained sixty-year-old, he can forget about any Esperanto.
But why don't you look for someone closer to your age?
Can you really fall in love with an old man like that?
Some people worry about love, some about bills.
In that case, the ad seems fine to me.
Thanks then.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Actually, this is nice, bro.
You have someone to talk to.
Bonan tagon.
What?
Sis, speak Czech here.
Do you have some secret language again?
It's Esperanto.
We have to speak it now in front of Mom.
Mom is bringing us a new daddy again and he speaks Esperanto, so he feels at home with us.
I looked for Esperanto-land on the map but couldn't find it.
I hope he's not Black.
Well, things are happening.
What got into her all of a sudden?
You got another back-payment notice for gas.
For electricity.
And how much?
A lot.
Have you seen him yet?
Yeah.
We have it stuck on the fridge with a magnet.
I mean the daddy.
Not yet.
We'd want someone we know.
Someone we like.
Ozzak?
No, Mom says it would be foolish...
She's not wrong.
Well, to marry your best customer.
Who?
You must be completely out of your minds.
I told you she wouldn't like it.
It's because of you.
Because of you, nobody would want such a dumb sister.
That's not true, Iva would want her.
Right, Iva?
I'd obviously want to, but you wouldn't want my father.
Why not?
He's sweet, takes care of everyone.
Takes care?
Everyone has to take care of him.
He doesn't care about anyone around him.
Leave me alone!
No, bro, this is serious.
You need to do something about your constipation.
Need something, kids?
We've been waiting here for an hour.
Sorry, I have a life too.
That's irrelevant, I need a regular rhythm.
You should have a regular rhythm of your bowel movements.
What am I supposed to do about it?
Can't you eat something that would help?
Like an orange.
What?
One won't kill you.
And we'd be done with it.
Both of us.
What'll it be?
Just have something that'll loosen you up.
Krusovice?
Don't have it.
Don't want it either.
You're not cooperating at all.
It'll come out eventually.
What?
I've got money in my belly.
Oh right.
Hey, couldn't he sell something else instead?
What if Ozzak without a kidney drinks less?
Without what kidney?
What are you on about?
Well, after all, he's your brother, it's none of my business.
How much does a wedding cost.
You're getting married?
It's any day now.
To whom?
His name is Emanuel.
I went to check him out today, I visited him in his tent.
Gross, so he's some kind of tinker?
An oxygen tent, in the ICU.
He's a doctor?
Better, a patient.
So you don't even know if he's a tinker?
He happens to be a powerful, educated and well-off man.
Simona, are you serious?
So what?
I don't know, this is insane.
What's insane are energy prices.
Two people wanting to get married is actually nice.
But you can't just rush into it, you need to get to know him first.
She saw him, so she knows him now, right?
I don't even know if I'd recognize him, I couldn't see anything through those glasses.
Why were you wearing glasses?
I put them on just to look smart.
He's looking for a classy woman.
With all due respect, don't tell me he didn't see right through you.
Today went fine, but by next time I'll need to cram a few things.
I'm just amazed at what you're willing to do for money.
Hello.
Tomas, now you've gone too far.
What?
You just walk away and take him with you.
I forgot.
Same.
The money.
God, what's that terrible smell?
You had to ask him.
How come?
When you're holding a ferret, you can't make sudden moves.
I was just covering myself.
You scared the poor weasel.
He sprayed right in my face.
Jesus, take it off, Iva will wash it.
You mean I'll have clean clothes again?
I'm not washing this.
And if the dry cleaner won't take it, you're burying it in the yard yourself.
Did you make him that dinner I told you about?
Prunes, bran, oatmeal, and sauerkraut?
Iva, it's for his health.
And our benefit.
It's spaghetti.
But it's made from white flour.
Do you know what that does to his digestion?
I don't.
And I don't care.
You should take this seriously too.
Do you know how the price of gold is dropping?
Just today we lost 10 crowns.
Good thing we're having spaghetti then.
Why?
They were on sale.
It's open.
Hey, what do you want?
We're here to see Mr. Pacovsky.
Hello.
What do you need?
Good grief.
We brought you a Bundt cake.
From Mom.
She baked it herself.
For you.
Pack up and eat that cake at home by yourselves.
Iva, what's gotten into you?
Simona's sending me a cake.
And she sends her regards.
Would you like to send regards back?
She doesn't!
So I get a cake and I won't even say hello back.
You're in a mood today.
Fine, fine, send regards too.
Thank you then.
Goodbye.
Goodbye and thank you so much for such a lovely visit.
You were pretty cold to them.
Because they're strangers and it's going to stay that way.
Ozzak, what are you up to now?
What?
I don't have other clothes and I'm not walking around naked.
Put it inside and when it's hermetically sealed, come get me.
Boy, what a fuss.
When we used to change her diapers, it didn't bother her.
No worries, I can't breathe.
Well, that weasel is a champion.
Why aren't you at school?
Estas jam vespero, patrino.
I don't understand you in that dictionary language.
It's evening, Mom.
Oh, then why aren't you in bed?
It's not that late yet.
It's that slacker hour between school and bed.
It's our sacred hour.
I don't have time, I'm studying.
We brought you a cake.
The ones from hell?
No, no, it wasn't Sasa.
Mr. Pacovsky sent it.
Tomas?
He's never sent me anything.
And he sends his regards.
He baked the cake himself.
For you.
Isn't that sweet.
Here, from the side.
Well, I'll thank him.
It's fine, we'll pass it on.
Don't you want to send regards back?
No.
I hope you're not expecting me to share.
You shouldn't eat before bed.
No, it's fine, Mom.
We just want to chat.
With me?
No, with each other.
Alright then.
Mr. Pacovsky is really nice, isn't he?
And caring.
Say something else.
And he has his own business.
Yeah, he does have a business.
Something else.
And I find him attractive as a man.
Yeah, I find him attractive as a man too.
Hey, either be quiet or leave.
Mom, do you have any lemonade?
No.
Not even in the back?
Sasa, why are you asking stupid questions?
Did Lexa hit you over the head?
He did.
But Mr. Pacovsky told him to stop.
Mr. Pacovsky is nice.
I'd better go to bed.
Me too.
Thanks for stopping.
When Mr. Pacovsky told me, I realized I was doing something wrong.
That's true.
Good night, Mom.
Good night.
You did that on purpose.
On purpose?
Look, the head just won't come off, it's stuck like this.
But he didn't have to growl at the cops.
I could've just told them you're not a bear.
Right, like I'm going to chat with cops.
Marcelka, why do you have a fur coat?
It's still warm out.
I don't have any other clothes.
And I paid a thousand in fines for walking a predator without a leash.
Want a straw with that beer?
No.
Well, isn't that great.
When it comes to beer, suddenly the head comes right off, huh?
But if you hadn't scared the weasel, I wouldn't have needed the fur coat at all.
By the way, great cake.
Oh, sure.
Sorry, I forgot to thank you.
My pleasure.
It was good.
It was.
What made you do it anyway?
I should be asking you that, shouldn't I?
I don't just give people cakes for no reason.
Do you want something for it?
Then I'm giving it back.
But I already ate it.
Come on, still going on about this.
Where would you have gotten it?
The kids brought it, right?
They did.
So what's the problem?
I just wanted to.
Say a normal thank you.
I already thanked you.
Hey, have you two been drinking?
Because if so, I want the same thing.
Yeah?
I don't want to be wrong about this.
And where's your home?
Can't you go here?
I'd rather at home.
Then hurry!
Ivuska, is Tomas here?
No, he's out somewhere with Ozzak.
Then I'll wait.
Not here though, they're probably at the pub.
I see.
Do you know if Tomas took any hazardous waste to the dry cleaner?
I only brought Ozzak's clothes there.
That must be it.
They called saying there's a chemical response unit there.
Problem?
But supposedly it's fine.
You just need to pick the clothes up tomorrow.
I'll swing by tomorrow then.
Between nine and eleven.
At the barracks gate in Liberec.
Well, Dad will be happy.
That you're not giving up on the clothes.
At least it would force him to wear something different.
Hey.
Good evening, Marcelka.
We just need to sort something out and I'll be right with you.
He won't do it for me again.
Come on, at least try.
I can try, but I'm not making any promises.
I don't need to be here for this.
Tomorrow drive to Liberec for Ozzak's clothes.
They couldn't clean them in Prague?
They said they only have a decontamination unit in Liberec.
Good Lord, fine.
But you're coming with me.
Right, of course.
Wait.
Does Liberec have a zoo?
Yes, it does.
A beautiful one.
Then I'm not going.
I don't want to end up behind bars again.
Don't exaggerate.
I'm exaggerating?
Last time I walked through Letna in a fur coat, a trainer caught me and I had to ride the carousel in the ring for a week.
If you'd gotten that zipper fixed, this wouldn't keep happening.
Maybe you could also try not wearing the head.
I'd feel naked.
Then Marcelka will watch him.
I beg your pardon.
Don't worry, Marcelka.
If it's like today,
no extraordinary events should be expected, right bro?
Fine, but I'm warning you, if anything extraordinary happens, I won't be part of it.
Marcelka, don't worry, we'll try again.
Right, Ozzak?
Yeah, but in a minute.
I need to sharpen my claws first.
At least take the head off.
Two people already ran away.
I'd get a draft on my neck.
Let's put up a sign: today's cashier is a bear.
Maybe some kids will come at least.
Try growling in a cute way.
Grrr, grrr, grrr.
Better not.
Hello, hey Ozzak.
Grrr, grrr, grrr.
Suits me, doesn't it?
Well Simona, you look like some kind of manager.
Easy now, Eman and I aren't that far along yet, but I could be a fiancee after today.
Is that for me?
Great, I'll put it in my purse.
That'll make an impression.
Aren't you worried it might come out during the conversation?
What?
That you're not exactly the college-educated type.
You're right, but my sister told me he's most interested in painting, so I spent all yesterday cramming the Surrealists.
The Surrealists?
Yeah, I know everything about Cezanne and Matisse.
About Cezanne and Matisse?
Yeah.
But they weren't Surrealists.
But they painted nicely, right?
Well...
Yes.
Then I won't mess up.
I'd rather let him do the talking anyway.
Well, sure.
If they've already taken the tube out of his throat.
That took a while!
What?
Here it comes!
No!
Yes!
I don't need to be here for this.
Stay!
I spent all yesterday afternoon sharpening my claws, so don't mess with me!
Fine, fine.
But I'll tell Tomas you broke loose from your chains!
Say it, come on!
I've got it.
I'll sign it Simonka.
I don't think we need to leave a note, he'll notice it's been cleaned up.
And he'll think Iva cleaned it.
What are you doing here?
Oh, nothing.
What would we be doing?
Well, you're alone in our apartment.
Your apartment?
We're in yours?
We honestly thought we were in ours.
Well then, we're going back to ours. Sasa, tell me the truth right now.
We came to clean up so your dad would think that...
Our mom cleaned it.
Clean up?
Because we already tried the cake.
It was already clean here.
Well, Iva, around that armchair needed a wipe-down, and you could dust the threshold more often.
Out.
Why did you draw a potato here?
That's a heart.
Can you stop behaving like an animal?
Where does it itch?
I've been in this hide all day.
I'm sweating like a pig.
Sorry I'm late.
Here, your clothes are inside.
Awesome, bro.
I feel like I've caught a cold from this bear suit.
I did what I could, there was terrible traffic.
Did anything happen?
Something did, but I know nothing about it.
Marcelka, I asked you to watch him.
I'm not a bathroom attendant.
Oh, Marcelka.
I'm not.
Ozzak.
So?
Almost!
But it smells like a doctor's office.
I don't think so.
I do think so.
Bro, lately you've had trouble calling things by their proper names.
Fine.
Got the gold coin?
I've got something.
My gold coin.
My little treasure.
What is it?
It feels kind of light.
It says: "Sorry, better luck next time."
Hopefully something else will come out.
Serves you right.
You miser.
Keep it, you cheapskate.
My bro is no miser.
But it was weird being on that toilet alone, bro.
Good thing it perked him up.
The finder of a gold coin hidden in Danone yogurt is slowly recovering from surgery to remove the coin from his body.
Police are searching for the coin, which was stolen during the procedure.
Iva.
What?
Stop being mad.
It was already clean here.
We don't want that old man.
Then tell your mom.
I don't know how to say "old man" in Esperanto.
Either way, pick someone other than my father.
But it would be so nice if we were sisters.
Yeah.
Just imagine.
We could be together all the time.
We'd do homework together, watch TV together.
And if you got married, I could be your bridesmaid.
You can be my bridesmaid anyway.
And we already do all the rest, don't we?
But it would be different somehow.
It sure would.
We'd prank each other and fight like you and Lexa.
He always starts it.
Sis, stop talking to them right now!
Abort Operation Cuckoo!
Why?
You could've just told her that a brother and sister can't marry.
Everyone knows that, right?
Exactly.
Can you imagine if we couldn't get married?
I can.
Horrible, right?
Sis, who was number two after Mr. Pacovsky?
The chemist.
Jesus, but he stinks.
He'll put up with it for us.
Sis, what are you staring at, another cake!
Get moving!
No, we'll manage on our own.
And as for those debts?
Lexa, can you still ride a scooter?
You never forget that.
Great...
Off you go then.
There's an audition at Beruska.
Here.
It was great, bro.
I'm glad I went, even on purpose.
Nobody's ever getting me back to Berousek's.
They've got this one really horny she-bear.
Oh, Simona, thanks for the tickets.
No problem, I got them for free.
There was a pony that could multiply.
You'd say two times three and it would stomp its foot six times.
Too bad you weren't there, Sasa.
You would've liked it.
By the way, where is Lexa?
Mommy?